So now that our add entry screen is all styled then set up and everything.
我们的添加条目屏幕已经设置好所有的样式
What I want to do now is let's go ahead and start working on our main history view,
现在我将设置主历史记录视图的样式
which is this view right here with the calendars.
也就是这个带日历的视图
And before we actually render any UI,
在渲染任何 UI 之前
what we'll need to do is we'll need to fetch
我们需要从虚假数据库中获取日历
our calendar from our fake database so we can get all of those things,
以便获取所有这些数据 所有这些项目
all of those items and then we could eventually render a calendar that looks like this.
最终我们可以渲染看起来像这样的日历
So to do that what we'll do is inside
为此 转到 api.js 文件
of our api.js file we need to go ahead and make another function,
新建一个函数
and we will call it fetchCalendarResults.
称之为 fetchCalendarResults
What this is going to do is we're going to call AsyncStorage.getItem.
我们将调用 AsyncStorage.getItem
Again, we're using AsyncStorage as our fake little database.
我们使用 AsyncStorage 作为虚假的小数据库
We are going to get all of the items which are living in the calendar store key property.
我们将获取位于 CALENDAR_STORAGE_KEY 属性中的所有项目
And then what we are going to do when we have
在将获取的项目返回给
those before we return them to whoever called fetchCalendarResults.
调用 fetchCalendarResults 的函数之前
What we're going to do is we want to
我们需要导入 formatCalendarResults
import formatCalendarResults which is coming from our calendar file.
它来自于 calendar 文件
Which we will go and format those,
我们将对这些设定格式
and then return whatever formatCalendarResults returns us.
然后返回 formatCalendarResults 返回的内容
So now that we have fetch calendar results we can actually go ahead and fetch all of the
获得 fetchCalendarResults 之后
day's or our entire calendar which are living in our AsyncStorage or our fake database.
我们可以从 AsyncStorage（即我们的虚假数据库）中获取整个日历
So now what we need to do is let's create a new file for our history.js component.
现在我们需要新建一个 History.js 组件文件
What I'm going to do is just paste in all this code which is just the typical.
粘贴所有这些代码 都是一些典型代码
We have a history component.
有一个 History 组件
It's rendering the text history and then we are exporting it.
它会渲染文本 History 然后导出它
So now, inside of our app.js file instead of rendering add entry,
在 App.js 文件中 我们不再渲染 AddEntry
before we get our router set up let's go ahead and render our history component.
先导入 History 然后渲染 History 组件
So now, if this works,
现在如果代码能运行的话
we see history up here behind the status bar.
我们会在状态栏后面看到“History”
So now what I want to do in history as I mentioned,
正如之前提到的
is we actually want to go ahead and invoke
现在我将在 History.js 文件中
the fetchCalendarResults function that we just barely set up.
调用刚刚创建的 fetchCalendarResults 函数
So what we will do here is let's import some stuff.
我们在这里导入一些组件
We're going to need to connect and then we're also eventually going to need some actions.
我们将需要 connect 还需要一些 action
If you remember, we have receive entries which is for
导入 receiveEntries
when we get our entries from the database.
表示从数据库中获取条目
And then we're also going to need add entry just
还需要导入 addEntry
in case we don't have any entries for today.
以防当天没有任何条目
We want to add the item for the current day.
我们需要为当天添加条目
Those are coming from actions.
它们来自于 actions
And then we are also going to need some stuff from our helper's file.
还需要从 helpers 文件导入一些组件
We'll use time to string and then we'll use get daily reminder value.
我们将使用 timeToString 然后我们将使用 getDailyReminderValue
Again, both of those are coming from utils/helpers.
二者都来自 utils/helpers
And then lastly, what we need is again,
最后 我们还需要导入
the fetchCalendarResults function that we built just a little bit ago.
刚刚创建的 fetchCalendarResults 函数
All right, so now what we want to do is when this component
现在 当该组件挂载时
mounts we want to go ahead and fetch our calendar results.
我们希望获取日历结果
So, before we do this,
在此之前
let's go ahead and connect our components,
我们连接下组件
so that we get access to the this.props.dispatch.
以便访问该属性的 dispatch
So we'll come down here and we will say,
在这里输入 dispatch
dispatch is going to be coming from the this.props.
它将来自于 this.props
And then let's go ahead and fetch our calendar results.
然后获取我们的日历结果
And then what we want to do,
然后
that's going to give us all of our entries.
获得所有条目
And then we can simply just dispatch
我们可以分派 receiveEntries
receive entries passing in the entry. So what's going to happen here?
传入 entry 这里会发生什么？
We call fetchCalendarResults, we get all of our entries and then we dispatch receive
我们调用 fetchCalendarResults 获得所有条目
entries which if you remember is eventually going to end up right here.
然后分派 receiveEntries 它最终将跑到这里
And we're going to take all those entries and just add them to our current state.
我们将所有这些条目添加到当前状态上
But, what we also want to do here is let's go ahead and chain a.then onto this.
但是还在这里输入 .then
Which will give us entries as a property on an object.
将 entries 当做对象的属性
Right here, if entries at time to string is not a thing.
在这里 如果 entries[timeToString] 没有内容
So if it's falsie,
如果为假
what that means is that we haven't entered any information in for the current day.
表明我们没有为当天输入任何信息
And what we want to do is if you remember back to
如果你还记得的话
our get daily reminder value method that we
在这里的 helpers 文件中创建的
created inside of our helpers file which is right here.
getDailyReminderValue 方法中
We basically want to set the property on
我们希望将 Redux Store 上的
our Redux Store for the current day to this value right here.
当天属性设为这个值
So what we will do is we will say,
我们要做的是...
if- this should be entries.
这里应该是 entries
If entries at the current day is falsie then go ahead and dispatch add entry passing
如果当天的 entries 为假 则分派 addEntry
it the time to string as the key and
传入 timeToString 作为键
the value is just going to be the result of calling get daily reminder values.
值为调用 getDailyReminderValues 后的结果
So again, what's going on here is we receive
这段代码的作用是接收条目
our entries if we don't have any entry for today.
如果当天没有条目
What we want to display is the little hand-wave saying,
则显示这个挥手图标
"Hey, don't forget to log your data today."
提示”Don't forget to log your data today!”
And in order to do that we need to go ahead and add
为此 我们需要将其当做属性
that as a property on our state under the key today.
添加为状态的属性 键为 today
So now, notice we don't have any local state here because
注意 我们在这里没有任何本地状态
the calendar state is living inside of Redux.
因为日历状态位于 Redux 中
So what we want to do real quick is let's get some space,
我们要快速设置的是…在这里添加一些空白行
and let's make a function here.
我们在这里新建一个函数
So we'll map state to props.
名称为 mapStateToProps
We are going to receive state which is really just the entries.
我们将接收状态 其实就是 entries
And we want to return all of the entries.
我们想要返回所有的 entries
So now if we pass map state to props to
如果我们将 mapStateToProps 传递给 connect
connect what we will get as props is all of the entries.
将获得所有的条目（作为属性）
So let's just go ahead and instead of rendering history,
我们在这里渲染 JSON.stringfy (this.props)
let's just render JSON.stringfy (this.props).
而不是 History
And so, now what should happen is when we run
现在 当我们运行代码的话
this what we should see is the components going to mount.
我们应该能够看到组件将加载
We're going to fetch some results.
我们将获得一些结果
We're going to update Redux with
并使用这些结果更新 Redux
those results and then eventually that will cause a re-render.
最终导致重新渲染界面
And so, we will see under this.props all of
我们将在 this.props 下看到
those entries we got when we called fetchCalendarResults.
当我们调用 fetchCalendarResults 时获得的所有条目
So, you'll notice here that we just have this huge object right here,
你会看到 在这里有个庞大的对象
which is everything that is coming in from our Redux state which is all of our entries,
表示 Redux 状态中的所有内容 即所有的条目
or basically our whole calendar.
也就是整个日历